mail-abuse.com 2007-08-28

# MAPS - Privacy Policy

**MAPS, a Division of KELKEA, INC.**

**Privacy Statement:**

Kelkea, Inc ("Kelkea") has created this privacy statement ("Statement") in order to demonstrate our commitment to customer privacy. Privacy on the MAPS web site, currently available at www.mail-abuse.com (the "Site") is of great importance to us. MAPS is a division of Kelkea, Inc. Because we gather important information from our visitors and customers, we have established this Statement as a means to communicate our information gathering and dissemination practices. We may periodically update this Statement. We will post the revised Statement on the Site and we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the Statement. Please check this Statement periodically to inform yourself of any changes. 

**Information We Collect; Use:**

We require individuals who register to use the services ("Services") offered on our Site to give us contact information, such as their name, title, company name, address, phone number, and e-mail address, and financial qualification and billing information, such as billing name and address, credit card number, number of DNS servers and the number of users within the organization that will be using the Services. At the time you express interest in obtaining additional information, or when you register for the Services, we may also ask for additional personal information, such as department name, fax number, or additional company information, such as annual revenues, number of employees, or industry. However, this additional information is not required to receive the Services and you can opt out of providing this additional information by not entering it when asked. 

Kelkea uses the information that we collect to set up Services for individuals and their organizations. We may also use the information to contact you to further discuss customer interest in our company, the Services that we provide, and to send information regarding our company or partners, such as announcements and events. You are invited to receive an email newsletter by providing an email address. 

All financial and billing information that we collect through the Site is used solely to check the qualifications of prospective customers and to bill for Services. This billing information is not used by Kelkea for marketing or promotional purposes. 

Kelkea may also collect certain information from visitors to and customers of the Site, such as Internet addresses. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our Site in order to constantly improve the quality of the Site and the Services.

We may also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers in order to improve our marketing efforts, to statistically analyze Site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize the Site's content, layout and services.

**Information We Disclose**

We do not disclose to any third-party the personally identifiable information you provide other than as stated in this Statement, unless we have obtained your consent. 

If you choose to provide us with your personally identifiable information, we may transfer this information within Kelkea, including any subsidiaries, affiliates and agents, as necessary to respond and process your request. Also if Kelkea is merged with or acquired by another company, sells a portion of its assets or otherwise goes through a business transition, personally identifiable information and other customer information will likely be part of the transferred assets.

We may share the personally identifiable information you provide with other companies we have hired to provide services for us. These companies are permitted to use the information we share with them only to perform the services we have hired them to provide. They are not permitted to use that information for any other purpose. For instance, Kelkea uses a third-party intermediary to manage the credit card processing. This intermediary is solely a link in the distribution chain, and is not permitted to store, retain, or use the information provided, except for the sole purpose of credit card processing. 

We disclose aggregated, non-personally identifiable information to advertisers and others for marketing and promotional purposes, without disclosing to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you. Certain information, such as your password, credit card number and bank account number, are not disclosed to advertisers or for marketing or promotional purposes at all.

In addition, we reserve the right to disclose any content, records or electronic communication of any kind (including without limitation personal information or private electronic communication transmitted on the Site): (i) to satisfy any law, regulation, or government request; (ii) if such disclosure is necessary to operate our business; or (iii) to protect the rights or property of Kelkea or its users, sponsors, providers, licensors or merchants. We also reserve the right to reject any order or to request additional information from any user. 

**Third-Party Sites:**

The Site contains links to other web sites. Kelkea is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other web sites. Customers and visitors will need to check the policy statement of these others web sites to understand their policies. Customers and visitors who access a linked site may be disclosing their private information. It is the responsibility of the user to keep such information private and confidential.

**Security:**

Although we will use commercially reasonable efforts as provided above to maintain the confidentiality of the personal information we collect online, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and we cannot guarantee that the personal information you submit to us will be free from unauthorized third party intrusion. 

**Opt-Out Policy:**

Kelkea offers its visitors and customers a means to choose how we may use information provided. You may choose to receive information from Kelkea on the registration form by checking the appropriate box. If, at any time after registering for information or ordering Services, you change your mind about receiving information from us or about sharing your information with third parties, send us a request specifying your new choice. Simply send your request to unsubscribe@kelkea.com.

**YOUR AGREEMENT**

By using this Site, you acknowledge and agree to this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to this Privacy Statement, please do not use the Site. We reserve the right to change, add or remove all or part of our privacy policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept such changes.

**Additional Information:**

Questions regarding this Statement or the practices of this Site should be directed to the Web Site Administrator at Kelkea by e-mailing such questions to [webmaster@kelkea.com](mailto:webmaster@kelkea.com).

**Contacting us**

You may contact us if you would like to:   

  * ask us any question regarding our privacy policy;
  * request a copy of your personal data, or change or delete your personal data; 
  * opt-out from receiving any future personalized offers or information from Kelkea. 

**Our Address**

You can contact us as follows: 

Attention: Web Site Administrator   
Kelkea, Inc.  
1737 North First Street, Suite 680  
San Jose, CA USA 95112  
408-453-6277

Last Updated: November 15, 2004
